Something to cool your head.
[JORDAN] I'm sorry, dude.
I just don't want you to experience
what happened with my mom.
They still haven't caught
the hit-and-run driver who hit her.
That's why I want Caloy to be caught.
And for Bea to be held accountable.
They have to pay for what they did.
[ROBBIE] Boss.
I think you've had too much to drink.
You know,
I was young
when I lost my mom.
And Grandpa…
With his condition,
I feel like I'm losing him too.
And now Billy.
I nearly lost her.
But she's safe, isn't she?
I just realized
how important she is to me.
I knew it.
She's like my family.
Her, Oliver, and Auntie Pres.
Ever since we were in high school,
whenever Grandpa had a gig,
he'd leave me at Billy's house.
Dude, you're eating three pieces?!
Save some for the rest of us!
This came from my grandpa, right?
Fine. Have as much as you want.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I don't like that.
- Oh yeah!
You like the drumsticks.
Peace.
Fine. We're good now.
Didn't I tell you yesterday
that I wasn't available?
You know, you just wasted my time.
That's not true!
If it's not true, let's go.
- Come with me. Let's go.
- Brandon, that hurts!
Bro.
Don't force her to come
if she doesn't want to.
You should go.
I'll call security if you don't.
[BEA] I also have a background
in marketing,
sales, and computer programming.
I am certain, ma'am, that I am qualified
for the executive assistant position.
[HR OFFICER]
Hmm… Okay.
We'll consider your application
and call you.
[CALOY] Hey!
Caloy?!
[BEA] You…
Why did you come here?
Someone might recognize you.
You know it's dangerous.
[CHUCKLES] Even you didn't recognize me.
Right?
I'm pretty good, aren't I?
[CALOY CHUCKLES] I'm really good.
You--
You don't have to worry.
I checked the surroundings.
[CALOY] No one was watching you.
Just me.
I was the only one.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA EXHALES DEEPLY]
'Bi…
Are you okay?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[SNIFFLES AGAIN]
[SIGHS]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Caloy, I don't understand.
I've done everything I can
to give my mother a good life.
[BEA SNIFFLES]
What's happening?
I'm back to square one.
I want Billy's life
because it should've been mine.
That should've been mine,
but Billy just had to steal it!
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[LOVELINE AGENT 1]
That's good news.
I'm glad my advice
the last time you called was helpful.
[LOVELINE AGENT 2] Hmm? Yes, Ms. P?
Any update on your concern
about Sir Brandon?
[KEYBOARDS CLACKING]
[LOVELINE AGENT 2] Please don't feel
guilty that you have other priorities.
There is nothing wrong with that.
A healthy relationship
is supposed to be supportive,
not combative.
If you two are arguing most of the time
and you have no time for him,
then maybe it could help
if you can pause and reflect.
So that you can decide
what's best for the both of you.
Right now, Brandon isn't being
persistent anymore.
I just really don't want us
to separate on bad terms.
But…
But if he doesn't want us
to have proper closure,
there's nothing I can do about it, right?
That's right, Ms. P.
Sometimes, the best closure
is no closure at all.
And sometimes, it's best to let
things unfold on their own.
Because most of the time,
things turn out for the better.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
[BEA SNIFFLING]
[SOBS]
We'll take it back.
Don't worry.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Like I've said before,
just use me.
Anything, everything you tell me to do,
I'll do it all.
I'll help you.
I'm here for you.
I'm right here.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Blank times negative 15 equals 75.
- What's this?
- Negative five.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Very good. Correct.
Number ten.
Mm-hmm.
Blank times 13 equals 65.
This one's easy. What's the answer?
Five!
- Very good!
- [GROANING]
Sleepy?
- I'm tired.
- Okay, all right.
Let's call it a day.
Let's do the rest tomorrow.
Very good!
Good night. Teddy!
- Okay. Here you go.
- Thank you!
Go to sleep, okay?
Let's do the rest tomorrow, okay?
- Tomorrow!
- Okay.
- Good night!
Good job!
Very good. [SMOOCHES]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
Auntie Pres.
You're still up, Billy?
[BILLY] So are you.
[PRECIOUS] My two-week leave
has been approved.
- Wow!
- That means
I can look after Oliver even if
he doesn't want me to.
- [BILLY LAUGHS]
- [PRECIOUS GIGGLING]
Auntie Pres, you can use that time
for yourself too, you know.
For when you want to take a break.
Hm?
And where would I go?
To the mall, or
to the salon!
- That's good too.
- [GIGGLES]
Or to go out on a date!
Hmm…
Do your agents report to you?
Isn't LoveLine supposed
to be a secure line?
Oh, it is, Auntie.
All LoveLine calls are confidential.
- It just so happened that…
- Hmm?
I was doing my rounds when you called.
- It was just a coincidence.
- Okay…
But thank you for trusting LoveLine.
But of course, Billy.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
So…
Do you… do you want to talk about it?
Hmm…
You know how our family is, right?
- [BILLY] Mm-hmm.
- Family first.
- Mm-hmm.
- If he can't accept that,
then there's nothing we can do about it.
[BILLY] Hmm.
There's no way I'd prioritize
going on dates with Brandon
when Oliver's safety is being
compromised, right?
You know, Billy,
when Rico passed away,
I poured all my love into you and Oliver.
Mm-hmm.
[PRECIOUS CLICKS TONGUE]
And I thought…
I thought that was enough.
Hmm.
Hmm…
So when Brandon came along,
I wasn't really looking for love.
- I wasn't expecting anything.
- Mm-hmm.
[PRECIOUS] When he came along, I thought,
"Oh, maybe I can still meet
someone again."
"Maybe this is it.
Maybe this is my second chance."
[BILLY] Mm.
I'm not getting any younger, you know?
And you…
You already have your own life.
One day, Billy,
you'll meet someone
and start your own family.
That's still a long way off.
As for Oliver, in a few years,
he'll be going abroad,
and he'll be moving out too.
So then I thought, maybe…
Maybe I need to too.
Maybe I need to have a life of my own.
- Since you have your own lives.
- Hmm!
But maybe I don't really
have a love story.
Maybe it's all just in my head.
Maybe I'm just imagining it.
Oh, come on! What are
you talking about, Auntie Pres?
- Don't mind me, gosh.
- Oh, come on!
- With a face like yours?!
- [PRECIOUS] Hmm!
- You're kind and caring.
- Stop!
- You're smart and a good cook!
- Hey, Benilda!
- Stop it.
- Seriously?!
Hmm?
- It's impossible.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- You know, Auntie Pres?
- Hmm?
I've heard so many love stories
- on LoveList.
- Hmm.
But do you know whose love story
I'm most excited about?
Yours.
Because you're someone
who gives so, so much love.
So I'm sure you'll get
so, so much love in return.
[CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY, SNIFFLES]
Have faith, Auntie. If you and Brandon
don't work out, so be it.
But if you're meant to be, then you are.
Oh, Billy.
You know, I don't want to
think about it for now.
Honestly, what we're
going through is no joke.
Anyway, what's the latest
with Caloy and Bea?
Uh…
Well, hmm…
They still haven't found Caloy.
As for Bea, the case is still pending.
Don't worry, Billy.
We'll protect each other.
Always.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, enough with the flattery.
- Just help me instead.
- You want that?
You want a hug?
- Sure, hug this.
- Okay.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
Okay, dude. Here's what I found.
Bea's mom's name is Mariela Mercado.
This is her hospital record.
She was confined for three years
in a mental institution.
I called the hospital.
Unfortunately,
all the records are strictly confidential.
But at least we know that her mother
has a history of mental illness.
That's serious, Jordan.
Maybe she really needs professional help.
That's what I'm saying, dude.
But there's nothing we can do right now
except be careful.
Thank you, Jordan.
Anytime.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
Yes, sir.
She's still outside.
Are you on your way?
Okay, please hurry.
[DOOR CLOSES SOFTLY]
[SOFTLY] Auntie Pres?
- [BILLY] Auntie?
- [PRECIOUS] Mm?
- Auntie Pres, sorry.
- [PRECIOUS GRUNTS]
[PRECIOUS] Mm?
A woman has been standing outside
for a while now.
Is it Bea?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING]
I can't make her out clearly.
- I'll check it out.
- No, you won't!
- Let's just call the police!
- They're already on their way.
- Huh?
- I'll bring this with me.
Just wait a minute, Auntie.
[DOOR CREAKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello? Chief?
[OFFICER] Ma'am, are you
the one who called earlier?
Yes, it's me. Where are you right now?
[OFFICER] We're already near, ma'am.
Okay. Please hurry up.
Thank you.
Why did you call the police?
I didn't come here to make a scene.
Ms. Mariela, please leave.
Billy, have mercy on me and my daughter.
[MARIELA] Let me in.
I'm just going to talk with you.
[PRECIOUS] Billy.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
MAMA
[OUT OF SERVICE TONE]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
All I have is Bea now.
My husband abandoned us.
My eldest child
has passed away already.
[SNIFFLES] I won't be able to handle it
if I also lose Bea.
Your daughter is the one
who started this mess.
Please, have some empathy.
She has done nothing wrong.
She was just jealous of her sister,
so she pretended to be Abi.
Ms. Mariela, this isn't just about her
pretending to be Abi.
Your daughter had our system hacked
before she even applied to our company.
I hope you understand that.
Don't accuse her of that!
You don't have any proof!
Wait a minute.
How well do you even know your child?
We are certain that Bea ordered Caloy
to trespass into our house!
My child was hurt
because of their actions!
Actually, Caloy and your child
should be in prison!
Liar!
I understand that as a mother,
you just want to protect your child.
But what she's doing is wrong.
And as parents,
shouldn't we teach our children
to do what's right?
We shouldn't be covering up for them.
But here you are, lying for your child!
What are you trying to say?
That I'm a bad mother?
I didn't say that.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, you're already rich!
Your life is so good!
But my daughter…
She just asked for help.
She made some small mistakes.
And you already want her to go to jail?!
[WHIMPERS]
Don't you have a heart?
[MARIELA] You have no empathy!
Not even a little bit.
We're just asking for some compassion.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Please have some mercy
and empathy, Billy.
I'm sorry, but I really can't
overlook Abi's actions.
Your life will change,
you bastard!
You'll suffer!
I can't bear to see you
suffer, my dear.
I'm not suffering.
I never said that
I was suffering.
I promise you.
I'll get back at Billy.
Could you come with me?
Is there really no way
we can look at Mariela Mercado's files?
I'm really sorry, ma'am,
but you can't.
Those are confidential.
[BILLY] Did you know that her mother
has a burn scar on her head?
Bea has a huge grudge against you.
[BILLY] I hope we finally learn why.
My family's safety is at stake here.
Oliver's lucky to have you.
Oh, I'm the one who's lucky
to have him and his sister.
29 Evangeline Street, Valencia.
This was Bea's old house.
[WOMAN] The rumor is that
Mariela's husband left her.